Guide to the John Betjeman Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 12.0 linear feet (10 boxes)
  - Unidentified film reels, Before 1971 (Box 22 (Oversize), Folder 605-607)